const questions = [
    {
      question: "1번/1번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "c"
    },
    {
      question: "2번/2번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "e"
    },
    {
      question: "3번/3번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "f"
    },
    {
      question: "4번/4번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "a"
    },
    {
      question: "5번/5번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "d"
    },
    {
      question: "6번/6번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "a"
    },
    {
      question: "7번/7번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "e"
    },
    {
      question: "8번/8번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "d"
    },
    {
      question: "9번/9번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "a"
    },
    {
      question: "10번/10번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "e"
    },
    {
        question: "11번/11번.gif",
        options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
        answer: "e"
      },
      {
        question: "12번/12번.gif",
        options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
        answer: "d"
      },
      {
        question: "13번/13번.gif",
        options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
        answer: "d"
      },
      {
        question: "14번/14번.gif",
        options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
        answer: "e"
      },
      {
        question: "15번/15번.gif",
        options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
        answer: "b"
      },
      {
        question: "16번/16번.gif",
        options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
        answer: "e"
      },
      {
        question: "17번/17번.gif",
        options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
        answer: "d"
      },
      {
        question: "18번/18번.gif",
        options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
        answer: "a"
      },
      {
        question: "19번/19번.gif",
        options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
        answer: "e"
      },
      {
        question: "20번/20번.gif",
        options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
        answer: "c"
      },
    {
      question: "21번/21번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "c"
    },
    {
      question: "22번/22번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "e"
    },
    {
      question: "23번/23번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "d"
    },
    {
      question: "24번/24번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "f"
    },
    {
      question: "25번/25번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "a"
    },
    {
      question: "26번/26번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "d"
    },
    {
      question: "27번/27번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "b"
    },
    {
      question: "28번/28번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "f"
    },
    {
      question: "29번/29번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "a"
    },
    {
      question: "30번/30번.gif",
      options: ["a", "b", "c", "d", "e", "f"],
      answer: "d"
    }
  ];

  